Guide to the Ipas Records, 1965-2020; 1965-ongoing RL.00617
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Executive and Management Files, 1965-2014; 46 boxes
  - Barbara Crane: Regional/country files 00-12 Afghanistan 02-03; Asia 01-06; Brazil; Cambodia 05; China 00-05; Europe 00-02; India 01; India 02; India 02; India dissemination seminar; India 05-06; India research; LAC region 00-01; LAC 00-09; LAC 07; Mexico GIRE 92; MENA 02-04; MENA 05; Nepal 02; Nepal 04; Nigeria 05-08; Nigeria documentation 05-09; Nigeria court program 08; Nigeria RH media 08; Nigeria 08; Russia 04; Stockholm Sida 05; Uruguay 04; Vietnam 00-02; Kosovo 02; US 00-02, 2000-2012 (Box 238)
  - Barbara Crane: Partners 01-12 APHA 01; pro-choice network 01; Rebecca cook 00-05; CRLP 01-02; PATH 01-04; IWHC 02; partnerships TIPS 02-08; Ctr for Repro rights 04; IPPF 04-05; MDG paper legalization 05; NGOs abortion; WHO 05; IPPF 06; MSI 06-07; Our Bodies Ourselves 06-07; Amnesty 06-08: IPPF SAAF 06-10; Athena 07; ACPD 08; Pathfinder 08-10; Global Health Council 09; Triangle Global Health Cons 10; IPPF SAAF 12, 2001-2012 (Box 239)
  - Barbara Crane UNFPA and World Bank 89-10: UNFPA pubs 89-93; UNFPA 96-02; UNFPA 02; UNFPA RH commodities supply 01-03; UNFPA kits refugees 05; UNFPA 05; UNFPA abortion 05; world Bank 07; UNFPA NYC 07; UNFPA 08; World Bank 08-09; World bank mtg on pop MDG 09; UNFPA 09-10; UNFPA Africa 10, 1989-2010 (Box 240)
  - Barbara Crane: Gag Rule, UNCPD, Nicaragua, MA, trips 00-11 Gag rule 01; gag rule 01; gag rule 03-07; gag rule 05; Bush Admin RH policies 03-05; abortion politics press conf 04; women's lens survey 00; UNCPD 02; MA 04-07; MA 04-09; MA background 09; judicial bypass mtg 09; Carbonnell 07; MDG summit 11; CPD 11; Brazil trip 07; Nicaragua 07; Nicarague 08; DC advocacy 07; DC trip 07, 2000-2011 (Box 241)
  - Barbara Crane: GSAC, misc mtgs, opposition 87-08 Intl Conf on Better Health for Women and Children thru fp 87 (2 folders); Working Group on RH & FP mtg reports 96-97; Conf on RH, Gender, Rights 00; Confounding the Critics Conf 99; key opposition 00-07; anti-choice 03-04; opposition 03-08; Conf presentations GSAC 08; GSAC conf 08, 1987-2008 (Box 242)
  - Executive Files: European Donors 05-12. UNFPA Briefing Paper 08-10; Eurodonors- General 08-10; SIDA Medical 05-08; SIDA Visit - Sept 08; SIDA Africa – March 09; SIDA- Alliance- Zambia May 09; SIDA Audit - Dec 2009; SIDA 09-12; Sweden 06- 10; Sweden Visit - May 12; Brussels 12; Finland 07-10; Finland 11 forward; Finland 09-12; Nordic Visit March 11; Norad Core 08; Norad General 09; Norad Sex Positive Apr 11; IDS Research Report 08, UK Policy Paper on Morbidity 09; DFID 09-10; DFID Policy Docs 09-10; DFID Malawi 10; DFID 10-11; DFID Tech Case Study 10; DFID Policies Ipas Input 10-12; DFID Annual Review 12; Netherlands Partnership Apr 10; Netherlands CORE - pre-11; Netherlands SALIN Mtg Oct 08; Netherlands Nov 10; Netherlands SALIN 11, Netherlands Oct 12; ASDD 11 (Box 230)
  - Executive Files: 03 - 12 EuroNGOs 11; Policy Retreat 03-09; Ipas Success Stories 06; Res & Policy & Comms 10; Ipas F/R Workshops 08; Messaging Resources 08-12; Planning Review 08-10; APHA 09; Partnerships 09-11; Washington Post Letter to the Editor 10; WHO 10; UNC SPH 10; Global Abortion Network 12; Declarations 01-07; Criminalization Dec 20; UNCPD 12; Women's Reproductive Choices 11; Logframe 09; Money Well Spent 10; Output 4 – 10; WEI 11; Team Building Exercises; Planning and Review 05; ICPD+15 09; Nepal May 12; GTZ Nepal Paper 11-12; Documenting Nepal 12; Vietnam 01-05; Cambodia 05; Nigeria and India Workshops 09; Africa Best Practices 09; Ethiopia Study Tour 12; Unsafe Abortion in Africa 00; Ethiopia Advocacy Meetings 03-06; Ethiopia May 07; Mexico Background Feb 05 (Box 231)
  - Executive Files 74-12: SOPs country offices – no date; Bank acct and corp resolutions 74-76; M Potts paper 75; org chart 87; Post abortion FP 91; complications 91-96; strategic plans 91-00; planning giving 94-97; articles by Ipas staff 94-10; endometrial biopsy 95; induced AB strategy 97; funding 98; Pop Council MA mtg 99; behavioral interviewing 99; results framework 00; MVA redesign presentation 00; Misoprostol group 00; MA background 00-02; staff presentations 00-06; NAF Mifepristone mtg 01; CFFC 01; Ipas docs/reports 01; ICMA formation mtg 01; emerging technologies 01; miso background 01; eurodonors 01-002; corres 01-03; conferences 01-03; MA 01-02; FCI 02; MA factsheets 02; Miso for PAC 02; Intl S/RR coalition 02; Intl Consortium on MA 02-04; drug access 03; March for Women's lives 04; individual donors 04; Second trimester 04; Gynuity mife mtg 04; Cordelia Scaife May 05; Continuum of Care 05-06; MVA sales 05-07; second gen training 05-07; IAWG refugees 06; Avian flu 06; OE 06-11; Henry David mem service 09; Petroni dissertation 10; Ipas overview 11; Harm reduction 12; reorganization 12, 1974-2012 (Box 236)
- Training and Service Delivery Improvement (TSDI), 1988-2009; 9 boxes
  - TSDI 88-00: Informed consent 88-94; TOT sessions 89; complications 91; APHA paper 92; international collaboration 92-93; framework for combatting unsafe abortion 95; AVSC quality workshop 95; management/senior staff 95-01; Egypt 96; PAC materials 94-04; AVSC consultancy 97; PRIME in-services 97; PRIME 98; FEBRASGO 97-98; African RH priorities conference 98; PRIME SOPs 98; division mission/vision98; misc corresp and planning 98-02; Frontiers 98-99; Brazil 98-01; Africa Desk 99-00; RHTP technologies mtg 99; TSDI country responsibilities 99; PRIME partners mtg 99; LAC Desk 99-01; PRIME performance improvement 00; TSDI management 00; infection prevention 00; PAC Scaling Up meeting working files 00; country summaries 00; APHA abortion task force 00; Zimbabwe PAC 00; Elective abortion mtg 00 (Box 114)
  - TSDI unit files: FY 01-02 Matrix management input 01; PAC PRIME mtgs 01; results framework 01; Scaling up toolbox 01; divisional management 01; Francophone consultant 01; TSDI surveys 01; redefining TSDI 01; objectives/budgets/planning 01; planning/workplans 01; US 01-02; SMT work 01-02; Bosnia MVA training 01-02; Adolescents 01-02; infection prevention 01-02; 2nd trimester abortion 01-02; patient-provider interaction background 01-02; Kenya plans/projections/report 01-03; Training Task Force 01-05; adolescent working group 02; training vision statement 02; abortion/early pregnancy failure 02; contraceptive counseling 02; RH for refugees 02; training tools and guide 02; HIV/pregnancy/abortion 02; new MVA rollout 02; Francophone publications 02; PAC curriculum workshop 02; ESPS baseline 02 (Box 115)
  - TSDI: 02 ESPS 02; planning 02; PP training resources 02; capacity building workshop 02; training best practices conference 02; 63iii/scale up/Eurodonors 02; EuroNGO Paris mtg 02; Peru PAC 02; medical abortion 02-06; scaling up presentations 02; training toolbox 02-03; Africa Alliance 02-03; Scaling up 02-03; training M&E 02-03; Francophone work 02-03; Francophone instruments 02-03; TSID unit management 02-03; TSDI staff mtgs 02-04; Community and abortion/PAC 02-04; abortion counseling background 02-05; pain management background 02-05; HBME - UNC 02-05; MVA Plus launch training 02-05; HIV working group 02-04; sexual/gender-based violence 02-04 (Box 116)
  - TSDI: 03 Kenya PAC baseline assessment 03; TSDI objectives 03; medical abortion 03; training numbers 03; monitoring 03; values clarification workshop South Africa 03; TSID retreats 03; South Africa 03; ICPD + 10 03; Addis meeting 03; decision-making table 03; Quality of care/service delivery improvement 03; midlevel providers 03; presentations 03; Francophone budget 03; SAGO Bamako 03; effective training events curriculum 03; PAC CMW training Kenya; 03; APHA 03; Kenya capacity building workshop & TOT 03; CD Rom of MVA plus 03; Global Trainer Network 03-04; Mozambique research study 03-05; Ethiopia team 03-05; "equip" of Equip & Train 03-05 (Box 117)
  - TSDI: 04-06 Vietnam 2nd trimester 04; essential elements of PAC model 04; TSDI global mtg 04; TSDI corres 04; Exec Team 04; Peru midwives 04; misoprostol for PAC mtg 04; scale up summary 04; legal and ethical case studies 04; sustainability manual expert review 04; GTN 04; planning and review 04; march for Women's Lives 04; EC 04-05; WHO strategic approach 04-05; Partnership for Safe Motherhood and Newborn Health 04-06; South Africa team 04-06; Global Health Council 05; TA & In-service mentoring program 05; GTN eval 05; performance improvement 05; MAP results 05; MVA Plus launch 05; QA 05; MVA regulatory 05; e-learning 05; MA Task Force 05; WHO small grants 05; Mozambique 05; training strategies learnings 05; PAC resources 05-06; US program 05-06; Tunisia 05-06; Evals of trainers' workshops 05-06; performance and quality improvement 05-06; APHA presentations 06; annual directors mtg 06; Compac 06; MVA processing 06; TSDI/PPD 06; Journal Club 06; GEM reports 06; WHO technical consultation 06; TA and Mentoring program 06; Counting Abortion so that Abortion Counts mtg and reference manual 06 (Box 118)
  - TSDI 2001-2006 Briefing paper Turkey 01; Gag Rule 01; EC Consortium 01; marketing 01; PRIME 01; TSDI toolbox 02; M&E 02; TSDI training workshop 02; trainers mtg evaluation 02; NYC training 02; launch needs assessment 02; TSID mtgs 02; COBAC 02; defining CAC 03; Brazil 03; Safe Motherhood IAG/TTF 03; APHA presentations 03; Kenya PAC trainees 04; WHO rollout mtg 04; Focus groups in research 04; MAP 05; SOGON 05; training numbers 05; Nigeria MVA/PAC workshop 05; training impact/scaling-up 05; Francophone midwives conf 05; training Tunisia 05; GEM 05; Safe abortion in Caribbean conf 05; GTN focus groups 05; Bolivia 05; TOT Argentina 05; global abortion trends 05; Brazil 05; Alliance 0-5; Ipas research 05; Nica 05; QA/QI 05; TOT subregional Bolivia 05; FLASOG 05; Tucuman Rosario trip 05; Bolivia/Argentina trip 05; FLASOG 05; processing MVA 05-06; Miso questionnaire 05-06; PPD training events 05-08; TSDI mtg 06; chile 06; IPPF Venezuela 06; Diclofenac background 06; ACEC mtg 06; Tunisia MA study trip 06; 2nd trimester Cuba 06; Cuba 06; strategic plan LAC 06; Mexico 06; TSDI objectives 06; ASEC NYC 06; Argentina trip 06; Panama 06; Geneva WHO 06; EC mtgs NYC 06; CD mtg 06; Bolivia e-learning 06; EC TSDI 06; values clarification 06; providers as advocates project 06; PPD/TSDI 06; supervision 06; Dialo web 06; trip reports Gomez 06; LAC MVA 06; EC mtg 06; TSDI visioning 06 (Box 140)
  - TSDI 2006 LAC Medical Schools Curricula Project notebook 06; Misoprostol notebook 06; Uruguay miso notebook 06-07; Strategic planning for TSDI notebook 06-09; WHO Miso working group 06-07; miso factsheet 06-07; Cuba 06-08; Francophone 06-08; Ghana 06-09; GTN 06-09 (Box 141)
  - TSDI 2007 ICEC mtg 07; NY Times nica 07; "magic number" 07; Cuba study 07; Centro de capacitacion 07; LAC M&E plans 07; TSDI survey 07; reports LAC pilot 07; GIS mtg 07; RWD MA 07; Miso LAC 07; Peru trip TA – IPPF 07; FIGO 07; Natl Advocates for Pregnant Women mtg 07; Tunisia study tour 07; WHO Miso Bellagio mtg 07; NAF 07; TSDI global mtg 07; Nica task force 07; OE 07; F-U providers/facilities 07; Entrevistas monitoring Nica Mexico 07; PMNCH 07; LAC pilot plans 07; PPD MVA 07; Uruguay 07; Mexico abortion death 07; HIV background 07; FLASOG 07; dossier 07; WHO mtg Miso guidelines 07; COMPs 07; Case studies workshop Egypt 07; MAC LAC Gynuity 07; CLAP 07; miso sales analysis 07; coaching 07; TSDI South Africa 07; Facilitative supervision and monitoring 07; MVA evidence 07; Africa performance review 07; TSDI general 07-09 (Box 142)
  - TSDI 2008-2009 VC for 2nd trimester RHM article 08; R&E global mtg 08; MSI safe abortion conference 08; Kat Turner workplan 08; Site monitoring results 08; VCAT workshops 08; preferred technologies mtg Istanbul 08; providers as advocates tools 08; MA LAC 08; MAPnet India 08; Bolivia indicators 08; Uruguay project eval 08; Supreme Court testimony Mexico 08; ARHP 08; SIP-A CLAP 08; UNC lecture 08; APHA presentation 08; PPCNC abortion patient forms 08; SEXADO 08; planning Gomez 08; Miso/mife mtg Valencia 08; FIGO UAW 08; Mexico study trip to NYC 08; Women Deliver and safe abortion conf 08; planning 08; grading evidence 08; LAC plans 08; clinical cases 08; TSDI workplan 08; PPD/TSDI 08; Nica project 08; MA curriculum 08; Cuba poster 08; PAFP Argentina student project 08; TSDI planning 08; Nica 08; Mexico pilot 08; FIGO WG 08; PPA workshops 08-09; Best practices Africa mtg 09; VCAT for donor 09; VCAT eval 09; PAA facilitation workshop 09; VCAT workshop 09 (notebook); global M&E data 09; GTN Nigeria/Ghana 09; Eval IPPF Safe Abortion Fund 09; QI 09; Africa MA TOT 09; TSDI Global Mtg 09 (Box 143)
- Policy Unit, 1991-2010; 16 boxes
  Progressive abortion policies are critical for women to be able to exercise their sexual and reproductive rights and have access to comprehensive, woman-centered abortion care. In 1995, Ipas acquired the first dedicated funding to broaden efforts in the area of support for policy reform which allowed the formation of a technical unit with dedicated staff.
  Areas of focus and impact for Ipas's policy work include: integrating abortion into the agendas of other organizations working in the areas of health, human rights, and empowerment of women, including advocacy with professional associations such as the International Confederation of Midwives (ICM) and the International Federation of Gynaecology and Obstetrics (FIGO); advocating for the full implementation and liberal interpretation of current abortion laws; supporting local groups advocating for reforming restrictive abortion laws; supporting and creating social movements at all levels (global, regional, national) for sexual and reproductive health and rights, with a focus on safe abortion; building youth leadership and capacity in support of sexual and reproductive health and rights, including safe abortion; and monitoring and countering anti-choice activism.
  Of note is Ipas's work with multilateral agencies such as the World Health Organization and the United Nations. In 1998 Ipas gained Special Consultative status with the Economic and Social Council (ECOSOC) of the United Nations which allowed for participation in international conferences and other UN forums. Ipas staff have worked since then with the broader NGO community to advocate for progressive language in UN agreements on sexual and reproductive health and rights, including safe abortion. The Ipas policy unit has also focused thematic work on neglected issues including the intersection of unwanted pregnancy and abortion with women living with HIV/AIDS, adolescents, violence against women, and human rights. Ipas's policy work on administrative barriers in laws and policies helped shape the policy recommendations in the groundbreaking WHO guidance on safe abortion issued first in 2003. Ipas's policy work was created and developed under the direction of Charlotte Hord Smith.
  - Policy: 91-06/Policy unit strategic planning/development: new issues mtg 98-99; strat planning 91; program planning 98-06; gender 00; Ipas strat planning 00-02; country team leaders mtg 03; strat planning 05; mngmnt training; results framework 00; org development 99-06; external unit eval 06; SMT 00-02 Donor documents: donor comms 96-06; unit corresp 97-01; donor reports/proposals 96-03 Special topics & neglected issues: MWIA 95; women's groups 95-99; USAID & fp 96; CAs/coalitions corres 97-03; community level 98-02; intl NAF 99; South to South partnership 96-99; refugees 98; Men & SRH 94-97; induced/elective abortion 96-00; human rights and RH group 96-02; adolescents 98-02; opposition research 97-04; Global gag rule 01; HIV/AIDS 00-03; HIV/AIDS monitoring tool 04-05; violence 00-04; sex selection 06; conferences and mtgs 91-02; midlevel providers 03 Presentations and mtgs: presentations 96-03; Africa regional trainers mtg 94; AWID 96 & 02; CIDEM mtg 98; WHO safe abortion conference 01; presentation for Med students for Choice 03 (Box 120)
  - Policy: 94-06 Country-Specific Policy Work: Africa 96-04; Africa Alliance 02-06; Africa newsclips 05; Bolivia 98; Europe 03; Kenya 00-04; Women's Health Project Kenya 00; Guyana reform 96; Malawi Penal review 00; Namibia reform 96-98; Poland 97-98; South Africa 96-05; Nepal reform 94-04; Thailand 04; Research and publications: PRB Honoring commitments focus group 97; Romania research and pub 94; Abortion/adolescents/AIDS pub92-96; sustainability 96; research/publications 96-03; Resources/tools for policy/advocacy: legal updates and issues 96-06; legal updates and issues/corresp 96-01; advocacy resources 98-06; ethics resources 00-02; policy and advocacy analysis and eval 04-06 UN ECOSOC special consultative status: UN NGO background 95-01; ECOSOC 95-06; ECOSOC Qtrly reports 02 (Box 121)
  - Policy: 97-00 UN: UN trip reports 97-98; UN contributions 00-06 Commission on Status of Women: CSW 98; CSW 99; CSW outcome document 00; survey of LAC women's orgs 98 Beijing and follow-up conferences: Beijing + 5 expert group mtg 98; Beijing + 5 98-00; Beijing + 5 prep mtgs 99-00 ICPD and follow-up conferences: ICPD + 5 98; ICPD + 5 99-00; ICPD +5 Hague forum; ICPD + 5 background docs 99 WHO/UNFPA/UNICEF/World Bank/UNGASS on Children: UNGASS on Children 01; UNICEF 97; UNFPA 95-99; WHO 96-04; WHO technical consultation on safe abortion 96-98; World Bank 97-00 (Box 122)
  - Policy:96-06 Gender Task Force: GTF 99-02, GTF newsletters 00-01; GTF workshop evals 01; GTF follow-up 01 Midlevel providers/midwives/ICM: midwives 96-99; ICM communications 96-03; ICM core competencies 99-00; SA midwives conf 01; ICM Vienna 02; ICM PAC statements 02-05; IHCAR proposal 01-03; core materials; ICM core competencies comms 99-02; ICM Brisbane 02-05 Gender or Sex curriculum/youth training in SRH issues: GOS 01; GOS TOT 03; GOS curriculum; gender and media exercise; gender/adolescents/RH training Training/service delivery/policy issues: TSDI/Health systems 92-06; medication abortion task force 02-06; MVA sustainability 02-04; youth-friendly services 04; IEC materials 06 (Box 123)
  - Policy 1997 – 2003 May 28th International Day of Action 94; May 28th 95; Policy objectives 95-96; May 28th 96; contraceptive failure proposal 97; ICM resolution 97; May 28th 97; AWID trip report 97; May 28th 98; FIGO recommendations 98; ICM 99; May 28th 99; Algerian women's orgs 99; potential policy projects 99; NY mtg trip report 99; m&E 00; policy assessment tool 00; policy overview 00; May 28th 00; ACNM trip report 00; presentations 00-01; policy analysis tools background 00-02; South Africa background 00-02; Social Watch 01; IFH video questionnaires 01; sexuality 01-02; Mozambique background 02; Rh laws and policies background 02; rights approaches 02; technology advocacy 02; Negal 02; UNGASS on children 02; Foreign Policy Institute 02; Ipas Sales vs advocacy 02; AGI U.S. abortion trends 02; advocacy tools 02; African abortion laws 02; Islam background 02; policy workplan 02; baseline assessment working groupo 02; Eurodonor policy indicators 02; mobilization local groups 02-04; presentations 02-07; Repro rights and wrongs presentation to CWPS 03; MSFC Ipas presentation 03; religious leaders/community work 03; repro rights donor 03; PP Global Partners and PP 03; NC policy and advocacy 03; US policy work 03; PAI gag rule project 03; U.S. Administration's ideological use of science 03; Lilian's list NC 03; US survey on barriers 03; CPD 03; SADC research project 03; Nigeria legal research 03; articles for US work 03; timeline of RR in the US 03; potential US partners 03; US tools 03; CEDAW 03 (Box 152)
  - Policy 03-04 UN Commission on Human Rights 03; CSW 03; UN and women's movement 03; War against women 03; provider testimonial 03; trip report 03; SisterSong paper 03; RH/RR & poverty 03; abortion in the media 03; ICPD + 10: Nica, Bolivia, Uruguay, Mexico, Nepal, Indonesia, Philippines, Malaysia, India, Europe; ICPD+10 Angela's interviews; ideas for donors 03; partners 03; Addis notes 03; Addis conf evals 03; ICPD+10 03-04: PAI's activities, booklet, minutes from mtgs, recommendations, Europe; Center for Health and Gender Equity 03-04; PPFA grassroots working group 03-04; Cairo resolution campaign 03-04; MDGs 03-05; ICPD+10 04: Asia, updates/statements, NGO documents and contributions to regional mtgs; FIGO panels/participants 04; GGR presentations 04; media training 04; March and intl subgroup 04; moving toward excellence model 04; MENA statement/SisterSong 04; Natl Advocates for Pregnant Women 04; Natl Latina Institute for RH 04; Natl Women's Alliance 04; Life in a post-Roe environment 04; natl network of abortion funds 04; unborn victims of violence act 04; Feminists for life 04; sex education in LAC 04; World congress of families 04; UNCPD 04 (Box 153)
  - Policy 04-06 FIGO survey 04; SC case 04; TAWG 04; Third Wave Blueprint for the Future 04; fetal rights 04; globalizing radical agenda mtg 04; presentations 04; ACOG and Ryan fellows 04; Intl FP Coalition 04; FF religious perspective 04; Rep Deborah Ross visit 04; Bush's other war presentation 04; abortion access project 04; policy retreat 04; SisterSong 04; F Coeyteux on global implication 04; ICPD+10 resources 04; ICPD+10 roundtable 04; ECLAC 04; Building pro-choice alliance in mexico 04-05; ARHP 04-05; SisterSong 04-05; Medical Students for Choice 04-05; policy proposal 04-05; youth attitudes US 04-06; LGBTQ 04-06; Bush's global war presentation; 05; SisterSong Mngmnt Circle mtg 05; Medical abortion terminology 05; Beijing+10 calendar of events 05; speakers' bureau 05; HR RH and Economic justice 05; FMF presentation 05; ARHP think tank 05; health and human rights background 05; IPPF working groups 05; WSF presentation and program 05; US Program 05; policy unit planning 05; Ipas report on Countdown 2015 05; ICPD+10 statement and activities 05; Countdown 2015 participants 05; Countdown 2015 media coverage 05; ICPD+10 Ipas packet 05; Abortion Workin Group media 05; NC Women's agenda assembly 05; US domestic restrictions 05; APHA Abortion Task Force mtg 05; impact of restrictive policies 05; US research findings 05; MSFC mtg evals 05; NLNI/CLPP 05-06; Feminist Majority Foundation 05-06; Women of Color 05-06; Natl Advisory Board mtg 05-06; Intl Women's Health Mtg 06; Brazil policy reform proposal 06; UN info 06-09; NC GOTV 06; Orange County Women's Commission 06; abortion technologies and women's rights 06; pro-choice education project materials 06; Environmental groups 06; US Policy Working Group 06; Expanding Ipas presence report 06; Choice USA conference (Box 154)
  - Policy 2007-2009 Providers as Advocates curriculum 07; Mapping our Rights 07; FIGO 07; Planning for Global Safe Abortion Conf 08; South Africa report 08; Muslim Women's initiative update 08; Advocacy workshop London 08; Kenya 08; Anti-choice Nigeria 08; Brazil 08; Alliance policy planning 08; Islam 08-09; Hesperian grant report 09; Ipas Vietnam Comm MA report 09; Nepal 09; Law reform East Africa donor proposal/report 09; AIDS conf poster 09; Cambodia 09 (Box 155)
  - Policy Unit 88-96: FHI/AIDS 88; Indonesia 89-98; US abortion research 90; B Crane paper/expanding access 91; FIGO Ed Comm 91-92; Interchange 92-96; Romania 92; Nigeria 92-96; abortion policy 93-98; Safe Motherhood 93-98; FIGO Ed Resource Ctr 94; PAFP VN talk 94; India background 94-97; SOFIGO 94-99; midwives comms 94-00; background 94-00; violence background 95; CEDAW 95; Guyana 95-97; South Africa 95-99; FIGO newsletters 95-00; India 95-03; POLICY Project 96-97; Access donor proposal/report 96-98 (Box 171)